The internet is a global network, whereas the world wide web is a system that utilizes the internet, via HTTP. Browsers are used to access web pages, including websites, text, sound, and other files. Other non-web forms of using the internet are e-mail (using SMTP), FTP to send files directly, usenet, and instant messaging.

DNS is used to give places a globally unique name-- though it is distinct from a place's location, despite a location and a DNS being able to describe the same thing (such as a webpage) simultaneously. It might be apt to refer to DNS as a page's digital location.

E-mail is the sending of digital messages, or the digital messages themselves. While there are e-mail services online (requiring a browser, as they're on the web), you can send email without being connected to the web, but you do need to be connected to a network.
