World Record Doughnut
Funding goal: $26,000

Have you ever wanted to be part of a world record, without having to figure out what to do and get up and go do it? Then this is the project for you! Every single penny given will go towards ingredients for a truly massive doughnut, larger than any ever made before.
All backers will be credited once the record becomes official.

$25 (unlimited)
Cast a vote toward what kind of frosting will be used!

$55 (unlimited)
Cast a vote toward what flavor of dough will be used!

$200 (4 available)
Choose what a fourth of the doughnut's filling will be!