I wouldn't say my view of (digital) technology has changed very much from this class, aside from becoming a bit broader.
I knew technology is very pervasive in modern society, but not often had I considered to what extent it affects life.
Specifically, those who work with it, and how much there is to know and learn about it; what it's made of, how it works, and how it got to be what/where it is today.
I've also learned to better appreciate the potential within mobile tech/smartphones.
They're not just phones anymore; it seems like when someone wants to talk with someone on a phone, it's almost no different than using a computer specifically to use Skype.
I admit that (part of) what I was actually hoping to learn in this class was specific skills rather than general concepts, though it did give me a better view of the paths I can take, which is another thing I was hoping to gain some understanding on.
